Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects
  - Motion Picture Projects
    - TWO + TWO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 132, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart, based on the novel by Martin Boris. Rev. draft, August 1979, 160 p.
    - TWO + TWO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 132, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart, based on a novel by Martin Boris. Second rev. draft, 12/10/79, annotated, 149 p. - Second rev. draft, same date, 125 p.
    - TWO + TWO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 132, Folder 3)
      Book by Martin Boris. Unrevised proof for publication by New York Times Books, 1979. Annotated by Larry Gelbart.
    - TWO + TWO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 133, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten draft, includes outline, no date, 195 pages. - Handwritten draft, includes outline, 148 p.
    - TWO + TWO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 133, Folder 3)
      Contracts and correspondence, dated 3/1/79 - 10/20/80, re payment for services rendered to Larry Gelbart from ITC Entertainment. 8 items.
    - UNFINISHED BUSINESS (Motion Picture Project) (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Notes on meeting. Revised for Columbia. 06/15/82 and 10/01/82. Annotated.
    - VENUS RISING (20th Century Fox, 1966) (Box 189, Folder 6)
      Screenplay. Draft, no author, 05/18/65, annotated, 153 p.
    - WIN A FEW, LOSE A FEW (Motion Picture Project) (Box 144, Folder 9)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. First draft, dated 7/26/77, 103 p.
    - WIN A FEW, LOSE A FEW (Motion Picture Project) (Box 144, Folder 10)
      Correspondence (5 items) related to the termination of dealings with CBS regarding the television pilot and commencement of negotiations with Sy Weintraub regarding movie, dated 10/74 - 8/77.
    - WIN A FEW, LOSE A FEW (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten draft, n.d.
    - WIN A FEW, LOSE A FEW (Motion Picture Project) (Box 151, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. First draft, 07/26/77, 102 p.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 48, Folder 7)
      "The Wrong Box," novel by Bernard Darwin, heavily annotated, marked" February 17, 1964" and "August 5th" - Writing agreements w/Columbia (Brit.) Prod., June 20, 1965, and Salamder Prod. 12/9/65.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 56, Folder 1)
      "When Antidisestablishmentarianism Was In Flower". Screenplay by Larry Gelbart & Burt Shevelove. Handwritten script, 145 pages, n.d. - Typescript, annotated, "The Wrong Box", 115 pages, n.d.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 56, Folder 2)
      "When Antidisestablishmentarianism Was In Flower." Script by Larry Gelbart. First draft, 144 pages, n.d.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 56, Folder 3)
      Shooting Script, August 1, 1965, 119 pages. Salamander Films Limited, Pinewood Studios. Written and Co-Produced by Larry Gelbart and Burt Shevelove. Annotated.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 56, Folder 4)
      Script, May 21, 1965, 121 pages.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Script, August 1, 1965, 125 pages. Annotated.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 57, Folder 14)
      Review clippings, 1966.
    - WRONG BOX (THE) (Columbia, 1966) (Box 57, Folder 15)
      Correspondence. 1965.
    - ZARKO! (Motion Picture Project) (Box 180, Folder 1)
      Articles (2 items) on Aristotle Onasis, one from Newsweek, 10/19/70. - Correspondence re story ideas, Sept. 1970, 7 p. - 1 page character summary, n.d. - Outline by L.R. Conbart, n.d., 26 p.
  - Musical Projects
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Scores with lyrics for musical numbers, handwritten. Music by Moose Charlop, lyrics by Norman Gimbal. Incl. one song with words and music by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller.
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Drafts of Act I: "original script", "second draft", "third draft". Uncollated pages for individual scenes, some dated December 5, 6, 7, 1960.
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Two revisions for Act I. - Uncollated pages for numerous revised scenes. Some dated in December 1960.
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Drafts of Act II: "first draft". - Scenes 1-11. - 2 sets of manuscript notes. Scenes 1-7 (incomplete). - Uncollated revisions of individual scenes, pages dated in December 1960
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Revised scripts, titled "The Hero", two acts. n.d. Book by Larry Gelbart, lyrics by Norman Gimbal, music by Moose Charlop, Robert Whitehead, Producers Theatre, NYC.
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Pages of revisions for Act I and II. Some dated in December 1960.
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Playbills, November 1960 - Jan. 1961 (New Haven, Philadelphia, Washington, D.C, New York), Souvenir Programs (2 copies).
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Congratulatory letters and telegrams, November 1960 - January 1961. Incl. one clipping/review.
    - CONQUERING HERO (THE) (Musical) (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Photographs, Moose Charlop and Norman Gimbal. 2 items.
  - Radio Projects
    - Abrogate, 2006 June - Nov (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Abrogate, 2006 May - June (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Abrogate, 2006 Jan - Mar (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Abrogate (Folder 1 of 4), 2005 Nov - 2006 Jan (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Abrogate (Folder 2 of 4), 2005 Nov - 2006 Jan (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Abrogate (Folder 3 of 4), 2005 Nov - 2006 Jan (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Abrogate (Folder 4 of 4), 2005 Nov - 2006 Jan (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Abrogate, no date (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 1-7 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Scripts, in chronological order, 9/14/48 - 10/25/48. For NBC Radio. Most scripts signed "Larry Gelbart".
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 8-14 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Scripts. In chronological order. 11/09/48 - 12/21/48. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #15-21 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Scripts. In chronological order. 12/28/48 - 02/08/49. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #22-28 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Scripts. In chronological order. 02/15/49 - 03/02/49. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 29-35 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 03/29/49 - 05/10/49. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 36-42 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 05/17/49 - 09/27/49. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 43-49 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 10/14/49 - 11/15/49. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 50-56 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 11/22/49 - 01/03/50. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 57-63 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 01/10/50 - 02/02/50. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 64-70 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 02/28/50 - 03/21/50. Most scripts signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 71-77 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 04/18/50 - 05/30/50. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 78-84 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 10/03/50 - 11/14/50. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 85-91 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 11/21/50 - 01/02/51. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 91-98 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 01/09/51 - 02/20/51. Most signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 99-105 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 02/27/51 - 04/17/51.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #106-112 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 04/10/51 - 05/29/51.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #113-115 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 06/05/51 - 06/26/51.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #120-124 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 10/31/51 - 11/27/51.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #131-134 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 01/15/52 - 02/05/52.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #139-142 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 02/26/52 - 03/25/52.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show #147-9 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Scripts. In chronological order: 05/06/52 - 05/20/52.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Publicity booklet (simulation of Life Magazine), cover autographed by people involved with the show, dated 1949. - Spiral-bound booklet with photographs and cartoons for the "Pacific Tour 1950".
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Sketches, dialogue, back spots, incomplete scripts. 1951-2.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Sketches, dialogue, incomplete scripts. No dates.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Sketches, dialogue, incomplete scripts. 1951-2. Some signed Larry Gelbart.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 18)
      Sketches, some titled, some dated, some co-written. Additional dialogue and Back Spots for individual shows, some identified by guest star, some by date. Folders 18-41.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 19)
      Folders 1-30: Additional materials (dialogue, back and middle spots) for specific shows, some identified by date or guest star.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 19)
      Folders 31-47: Miscellaneous materials for titled and untitled sketches, identified by guest star, location of show, seldom by date.
    - BOB HOPE SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 20)
      Sketches, back spots, additional dialogue, some dated between 1949-1952), some titled. 63 folders.
    - COMMAND PERFORMANCE (Radio)Show #234-243 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Radio scripts for the Armed Forces Radio Service, by Larry Gelbart et al. Volume I: June 18 - August 20, 1946. [Several signed by Larry Gelbart]
    - COMMAND PERFORMANCE (Radio)Show #244-249, #252-254 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Radio scripts by Larry Gelbart, et al., Volume II: August 27 - November 5, 1946. [Most signed by Larry Gelbart]
    - COMMAND PERFORMANCE (Radio)Show #255, #257-262, #268-270 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Radio scripts by Larry Gelbart, et al., November 12, 26, 1946 - January 2, 1947, February 11- 25, 1947. [Most signed by Larry Gelbart]
    - COMMAND PERFORMANCE (Radio)Show #271-279, #336 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Radio scripts by Larry Gelbart, et al., March 4 - April 29,1947, June 15, 1948. [Most signed by Larry Gelbart]
    - COMMAND PERFORMANCE (Radio) (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Christmas 1946. Script by Larry Gelbart, et al., dated September 9, 1946. [Signed Larry Gelbart]
    - DUFFY'S TAVERN (Radio) (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Scripts, signed "Larry Gelbart", September 21 - November 21, 1945. 10 episodes. - Script for Preview, April 25, 1945.
    - DUFFY'S TAVERN (Radio) (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Scripts, signed "Larry Gelbart", November 29, 1945 - February 1, 1946. 10 episodes.
    - DUFFY'S TAVERN (Radio) (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Scripts, signed "Larry Gelbart", February 8 - April 17, 1946. 11 episodes.
    - DUFFY'S TAVERN (Radio) (Box 26, Folder 8)
      Scripts, nos 1-10, by Larry Gelbart, et al., October 2 - December 4, 1946. [Signed "Larry Gelbart"]
    - DUFFY'S TAVERN (Radio) (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Scripts, nos. 11-21, by Larry Gelbart, et al., December 11, 1946-February 19, 1947. [Signed "Larry Gelbart"]
    - DUFFY'S TAVERN (Radio) (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Script materials by Larry Gelbart, Sid Dorfman, and Vince Bogert for 1st, 2nd, 3rd spots and monologues. 1945-1946.
    - GINNY SIMMS SHOW (THE) (Radio)Show # 26 (Box 151, Folder 13)
      Script: Draft, No author, 03/14/47, 24 p. Produced by the Borden Company.
    - JACK PAAR PROGRAM (THE) (Radio)"Audition" (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart, Sid Dorfman and Larry Marks. Dated 03/11/47 and 04/11/47. Signed by Larry Gelbart.
    - JACK PAAR PROGRAM (THE) (Radio)Program #1 - #3 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Scripts, signed Larry Gelbart. #1 (06/01/47), #2 (06/08/47), #3 (06/15/47).
    - JACK PAAR PROGRAM (THE) (Radio)Program #4 - #7 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Scripts, signed by Larry Gelbart. #4 ( 06/22/47), #5 (06/29/47), #6 (06/29/47), #7 (07/13/47).
    - JACK PAAR PROGRAM (THE) (Radio)Program #8 - #10 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Scripts, signed by Larry Gelbart #8 (07/20/47), #9 (07/27/47), #10 (08/03/47).
    - JOAN DAVIS SHOW (THE) (Radio)Episodes #27-39 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      Scripts dated 03/31/47 - 06/27/47. Name credit for staff, including writers, and cast listed for each show. All scripts signed by Larry Gelbart.
    - JUNIOR AD CLUB SPOTLIGHT ON ACHIEVEMENT (Radio) (Box 173, Folder 1)
      Script #9, no author, no date, 8 pages.
    - KENNY KAYE BAKER SHOW (THE) (Radio) (Box 180, Folder 8)
      Script: Draft, no author, no date, annotated, 30 p.
    - MASTERGATE (Radio) (Box 52, Folder 3)
      "A Play on Words" by Larry Gelbart. Two scripts, both dated 03/15/92. Each is heavily but differently annotated.
    - MASTERGATE (Radio) (Box 52, Folder 5)
      "A Play on Words" by Larry Gelbart. Radio scripts. Both dated 03/15/92. One labeled "Original." Some annotations.
    - MASTERGATE (Radio) (Box 52, Folder 7)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 08/01/89.
    - MASTERGATE (Radio) (Box 55, Folder 4)
      "A Play on Words" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 10/12/89, marked "Recording Version." Annotated.
    - SEALTEST VILLAGE STORE PROGRAM (Radio)Show #418 - #427 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Scripts, signed Larry Gelbart. Dated 04/29/48 - 07/08/48.
    - SEALTEST VILLAGE STORE PROGRAM (Radio)Show #386 - #392 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Scripts, signed Larry Gelbart. Dated 09/11/47 - 10/23/47.
    - SEALTEST VILLAGE STORE PROGRAM (Radio)Show # 393 - #399 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Scripts, signed Larry Gelbart. Dated 10/30/47 - 12/11/47.
    - SEALTEST VILLAGE STORE PROGRAM (Radio)Show #400 - #407 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Scripts, signed Larry Gelbart. Dated 12/18/47 - 02/05/48.
    - SEALTEST VILLAGE STORE PROGRAM (Radio)Show #408 - #417 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Scripts, signed Larry Gelbart. Dated 02/12/48 - 04/22/48.
  - Stage Projects
    - Power Failure, 1999-2000 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Power Failure, 1999 June (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Power Failure, 1999 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Power Failure - script, 1998 Dec 7 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Power Failure (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-1993 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Power Failure (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Power Failure (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Power Failure (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - 1,2,3,4,5 - scripts, 1987 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - 1,2,3,4,5, 1998-1999 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Pinocchio, 1999 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - My LA, c. 1949 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Star is Born (A), 1997-1999 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Star is Born (A), 1953 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Buzz!! (Folder 1 of 2), 2000, 2002 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Buzz!! (Folder 2 of 2), 2000,2002 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Buzz!!, 2002 June-Aug (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 2001-2002 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - City of Angels, 1998-2002 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Buzz!!, 2002 Aug - Oct (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - City of Angels, 2002 Aug - Nov (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Napoleon and Josephine (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Napoleon and Josephine (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Napoleon and Josephine, 2000 Jan - May (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Napoleon and Josephine, 2001 May - 2002 Jan (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Napoleon and Josephine, 1999 Aug - 2000 Apr (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Buzz!!, 2000-2001 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Buzz!!, 1999-2001 (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Buzz!!, 2001 Aug - Oct (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - City of Angels, 2000 Nov - 2001 June (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Buzz!!, 1999 July - 2000 May (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Buzz!!, 1999 Dec - 2000 May (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 1998-1999 (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 1999 (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 1998-2000 (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 1998 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 2000-2001 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Sly Fox, 1998-2000 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Sly Fox, 2000-2002 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Sly Fox, 1976 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Sly Fox, 2000-2003 (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - City of Angels, 2002 Nov - 2003 Jan (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - City of Angels (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 Jan, 2003 Feb (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - City of Angels (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 Jan, 2003 Feb (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - City of Angels, 2002 July - 2003 Aug (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - City of Angels, 2003 Jan - Mar (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Buzz!!, 2003 June - Oct (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Buzz!!, 2002 Oct - 2003 June (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Like Jazz (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 Aug - 2003 Oct (Box 262, Folder 2)
      Also known as Making Music, In the Pocket, Up Close and Musical.
    - Like Jazz (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 Aug - 2003 Oct (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Oct (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Sept - Oct (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Like Jazz (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 July - 2003 May (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Like Jazz (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 July - 2003 May (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Napoleon and Josephine, 2002-2003 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 1 of 3), 2001 Aug - Dec (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 2 of 3), 2001 Aug - Dec (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 3 of 3), 2001 Aug - Dec (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A) (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 May - Aug (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A) (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 May - Aug (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 1 of 3), 2001 Oct - 2002 Mar (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 2 of 3), 2001 Oct - 2002 Mar (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 3 of 3), 2001 Oct - 2002 Mar (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Lysistrata, 2001-2003 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 1 of 2), 2001 Sept (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 Sept (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Lysistrata - script, 2001 Oct 8 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Lysistrata - script, 2001 Oct 24 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Lysistrata - script, 2002 Jan 17 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Lysistrata, 2003 July - 2004 May (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Sly Fox, 2003 Dec - 2004 Mar (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Sly Fox, 2003 May - June (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 Jan (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 Feb (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 Mar - April (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 Mar (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Sly Fox, 2003 Feb - Nov (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 Apr (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Sly Fox (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 Apr - May (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Sly Fox (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 Apr - May (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 Apr - May (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - City of Angels, 2003-2004 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Tootsie (the Musical), 2003 June - 2004 May (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Oct - Nov (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Dec - 2004 Jan (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Nov - Dec (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Dec - 2004 Apr (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Lysistrata, 2002-2004 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 2002-2004 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 2004 Jan - May (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Sly Fox, 2003 Dec - 2004 Jan (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Buzz!!, 2003-2005 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - City of Angels, 2005 Nov - Dec (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - City of Angels, 2004-2005 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - City of Angels, 2005 Nov (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - City of Angels, 2005 July - Nov (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - City of Angels - script, 2002 Jan 22 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Floodgate - script, 2005 Nov (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Nov (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Nov (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Oct - Nov (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Floodgate - script, 2005 Oct 25 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Floodgate - script, 2005 Oct 20 (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Nov - Dec (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Oct (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Floodgate - script, 2005 Oct 25 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 2004 July - Nov (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Sly Fox, 2004 July - Aug (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Sly Fox (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 June - Aug (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Sly Fox (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 June - Aug (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - In the Pocket, 2005 Jan - Mar (Box 302, Folder 4)
      Also known as Like Jazz, Making Music, Up Close and Musical.
    - In the Pocket, 2005 Jan - Mar (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - In the Pocket, 2004 Dec - 2005 Mar (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - In the Pocket, 2005 Apr - June (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Like Jazz - script, 2003 Dec 4 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - Like Jazz, 2004 Aug - Nov (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Like Jazz, 2003 Sept - 2004 Sept (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - Like Jazz, 2004 Sept - Nov (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Like Jazz, 2004 Sept - Dec (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Lysistrata, 2002 May (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 1 of 3), 2001-2003 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 2 of 3), 2001-2003 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 3 of 3), 2001-2003 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Lysistrata, 2004 Aug 1 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 1 of 2), 2001 May - 2002 Feb (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Lysistrata (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 May - 2002 Feb (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Lysistrata, 2004 July - 2005 Jan (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Power Failure, 1991, 2004-2005 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Tootsie (the Musical), 2004-2005 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Best Is Yet to Come (The), 2007 Feb - Apr (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Better Late, 2007 June - Aug (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Better Late, 2007 May - June (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Gulliver, 1999 Feb 4 (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Buzz!!, 2006 May - Aug (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - City of Angels, 2005 Nov - 2006 Oct (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - City of Angels (Folder 1 of 2), 2005 Dec - 2006 Feb (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - City of Angels (Folder 2 of 2), 2005 Dec - 2006 Feb (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Dead Boy by Craig Wright, 2006 May (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Floodgate, 2006 Feb - Mar (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Floodgate - script, 2005 Nov 22 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Dec (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Floodgate - New Orleans Production, ca. 2006 Mar (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Dec - 2006 Jan (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Floodgate, 2006 Mar - Apr (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Oct (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Floodgate, 2005 Dec (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Floodgate script, 2005 December 20 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Floodgate, 2006 Mar - May (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Floodgate, 2006 Apr - Nov (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (A), 2004-2006 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Gulliver, no date (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - In the Pocket, 2005 June - Dec (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - In the Pocket - script, 2005 June 16 (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - In the Pocket, 2005 Dec - 2006 Jan (Box 317, Folder 1)